ILGWU Montreal Joint Board Records 5780/116
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Local 342, 1955-1964 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Local 112, 1971-1975 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Local 112, 1965-1970 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Local 112, 1955-1964 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Joint Council: Annual Reports, 1955-1962 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Joint Council: Annual Reports, 1951-1954 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Constitution: ILGWU, 1937-1957 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Joint Council: Annual Reports, 1951-1958 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Joint Council: Minutes, 1973-1975 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Joint Council: Minutes, 1967-1973 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Board of Directors: Minutes, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Decree, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Stulberg, Louis: President, 1966-1971 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Stulberg, Louis: President, 1969-1970 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Union Label Correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Union Label Correspondence, 1963-1971 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Union Label Correspondence, 1958-1962 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Louis Stulberg, Secretary-Treasurer, ILGWU, 1968-1969 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Louis Stulberg, Secretary-Treasurer, ILGWU, 1966-1968 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Louis Stulberg, Secretary-Treasurer, ILGWU, 1961-1965 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Louis Stulberg, Secretary-Treasurer, ILGWU, 1958-1961 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Louis Stulberg, Secretary-Treasurer, ILGWU, 1956-1958 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Organization Campaign, 1958-1959 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Organization Campaign, 1958-1960 (Box 4.1, Folder 1)
  French - this folder was formerly in box 4, ff 20, box 4 was overfull and splitting at the seams, so a few folders were moved to a new box
- Organization Campaign, 1955-1960 (Box 4.1, Folder 2)
  French - this folder was formerly in box 4, ff 21, box 4 was overfull and splitting at the seams, so a few folders were moved to a new box
- Organization Campaign, 1955-1963 (Box 4.1, Folder 3)
  French - this folder was formerly in box 4, ff 22, box 4 was overfull and splitting at the seams, so a few folders were moved to a new box
- Royal Commissions on Canadian Economic Prospects, 1956-1957 (Box 4.1, Folder 4)
  - this folder was formerly in box 4, ff 23, box 4 was overfull and splitting at the seams, so a few folders were moved to a new box
- Royal Commission on Canadian Economic Prospects, 1956-1960 (Box 4.1, Folder 5)
  - this folder was formerly in box 4, ff 24, box 4 was overfull and splitting at the seams, so a few folders were moved to a new box
- Fontaine' Robert, 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Letters Regarding ILGWU, 1930-1935 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Letters Regarding ILGWU, 1935 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Letters Regarding ILGWU, 1935 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Letters Regarding ILGWU, 1930-1935 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Constitution: Translation into French, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- General Executive Board Reports, 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Grievance Committee, 1974-1976 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Human Rights, 1972-1976 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Montreal Joint Board, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Copies of Minutes - Joint Board, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Copies of Minutes - Joint Board, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Board of Directors - Appeals, 1972-1976 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Joint Board - Special Investigation Committee, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Joint Commission - General, 1972-1977 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Joint Commission - Decree, 1968-1977 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Joint Commission: Financial Statements from Auditors, 1971-1976 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Joint Commission - Levy, 1972-1975 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Joint Council - Minutes, 1975-1977 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Luigi Infantino, 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- Luigi Infantino, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- Incoming Mail, 1944-1945 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- Incoming Mail, 1943-1944 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- Incoming Mail, 1944-1954 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- Letters Regarding ILGWU, 1945-1946 (Box 5, Folder 25)
- Letters Regarding ILGWU, 1944-1945 (Box 5, Folder 26)
- Letters Regarding ILGWU, 1940-1945 (Box 5, Folder 27)
- Incoming Mail, 1940 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Incoming Mail, 1939-1940 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Incoming Mail, 1939 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Incoming Mail, 1938-1939 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Incoming Mail, 1938 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Incoming Mail, 1944-1947 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Incoming Mail, 1947-1949 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Incoming Mail, 1947-1949 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Incoming Mail, 1939-1943 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Incoming Mail, 1941-1943 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Incoming Mail, 1940-1941 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Incoming Mail, 1943 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Incoming Mail, 1943 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Incoming Mail, 1943 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Incoming Mail, 1942 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Incoming Mail, 1942 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Incoming Mail, 1940-1942 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Incoming Mail, 1941-1942 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Fifteenth Anniversary Local 262, 1952-1977 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Decree, 1955-1971 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Elections - 1977; Nomination Meetings (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Elections - 1977; Nomination Meetings (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Elections - 1977; Nomination Meetings (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Cutler, Phil, Q.C., 1977 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Elections - 1977 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Incoming Mail, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Incoming Mail, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Incoming Mail, 1976-1977 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Board of Directors: Dress, 1976-1977 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Board of Directors, 1976-1977 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Board of Directors, 1976-1977 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Canadian Co-coordinating Conference, 1961 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Co-coordinating, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Correspondence with New York, 1974-1977 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Canadian Labour Congress - Trials, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 17)
- Canadian Coordinating Conference, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  May 1-2, 1976
- Canadian Coordinating Conference, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 19)
- Canadian Coordinating Conference, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 20)
- Local 43 Correspondence, 1978-1979 (Box 7, Folder 21)
- Local 43 Copies of Minutes, 1978-1979 (Box 7, Folder 22)
- Local 43 Form Letters: Re Meetings (Box 7, Folder 23)
- Local 19 Form Letters: Re Meetings (Box 7, Folder 24)
- Local 19 Correspondence, 1978-1980 (Box 7, Folder 25)
- Local 19 Copies of Minutes, 1978-1980 (Box 7, Folder 26)
- Spector, Charles, 1978-1980 (Box 7, Folder 27)
- Decarey, Jasmin, Rivest Et Laurin, 1978-1979 (Box 7, Folder 28)
- Cutler, Phil, Q.C., 1977-1980 (Box 7, Folder 29)
- Legal Action, 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 30)
- Education Department - Booklets, 1962-1964 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Education Department - Booklets, 1961-1970 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Education Department - Booklets, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Legal, 1979-1980 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Local 61: Copies of Minutes, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Local 61: Correspondence, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Local 61 Form Letters, Re: Meetings (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Local 112 Copies of Minutes, 1978-1980 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Local 112: Correspondence, 1978-1980 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Local 112 Form Letters, Re: Meetings, 1980-1981 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Local 113, 1979-1980 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Local 205, 1980-1981 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Local 205: Minutes, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Local 205: Process-Verbal, 1979-1980 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Local 205: Process-Verbal, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- Local 205: Process-Verbal, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 16)
- Local 205 Correspondence, Re: Meetings, 1978-1980 (Box 8, Folder 17)
- Local 241, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 18)
- Local 245, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 19)
- Local 246, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 20)
- Local 247, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 21)
- Local 262 Copies of Minutes, 1978-1980 (Box 8, Folder 22)
- Local 262 Correspondence, Re: Meetings, 1978-1981 (Box 8, Folder 23)
- Local 262 - Grievance Correspondence, 1978-1981 (Box 8, Folder 24)
- Local 262 - Grievance CTEE Meetings (Box 8, Folder 25)
- Local 248, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 26)
- New Democratic Party, 1956-1961 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- New Democratic Party, 1961-1963 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- New Democratic Party, 1950-1961 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Convention Reports, 1952-1960 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Convention Reports, 1940-1952 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Union Label Correspondence, 1964-1966 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Union Label Correspondence, 1963-1964 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Union Label Correspondence, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Norman Olson, Associates Ltd., 1977 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Officers Meetings, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Correspondence, 1946-1964 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Correspondence, 1960-1964 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- Guild: Correspondence, Re: Members, 1948 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Guild: Correspondence, Re: Members, 1947-1948 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Guild Correspondence, Re: Members, 1947 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Correspondence, 1949 (Box 9, Folder 16)
- Correspondence, 1949 (Box 9, Folder 17)
- Correspondence with Other Unions, 1975-1976 (Box 9, Folder 18)
- Guild - Correspondence, Re: Members, 1953-1965 (Box 9, Folder 19)
- Guild - Correspondence, Re: Members, 1950-1953 (Box 9, Folder 20)
- Correspondence, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 21)
- Correspondence, 1956-1958 (Box 9, Folder 22)
- Correspondence, 1958-1959 (Box 9, Folder 23)
- Correspondence, 1954-1959 (Box 9, Folder 24)
- Correspondence, 1952-1954 (Box 9, Folder 25)
- Correspondence, 1949-1952 (Box 9, Folder 26)
- Joint Council Minutes, 1968-1975 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Joint Council Minutes, 1964-1970 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Joint Council Minutes, 1968-1972 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Annual Reports, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Severance Pay Fund, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Memorandum of Agreement, 1958-1960 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Memorandum of Agreement, 1960-1964 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Memorandum of Agreement, 1960-1967 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Memorandum of Collective Agreements, 1963-1966 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Memorandum of Collective Agreements, 1960-1966 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Memorandum of Collective Agreements, 1960 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Memorandum of Collective Agreements, 1960-1963 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Canadian Coordinating Conference, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  November 19-21
- Imports, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Imports, 1976-1977 (Box 10, Folder 15)
- Imports, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 16)
- Imports, 1974-1976 (Box 10, Folder 17)
- Special Committee, 1975-1977 (Box 10, Folder 18)
- Special Committee, 1976-1977 (Box 10, Folder 19)
- Banquet Re: Mr. Shane: 80th Birthday, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Banquet Re: Mr. Shane, 80th Birthday (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Banquet, Re: Mr. Shane: 80th Birthday (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Banquet, Re: Mr. Shane: 80th Birthday, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Banquet, Re: Mr. Shane: 80th Birthday, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Banquet, Re: Mr. Shane: 80th Birthday, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Banquet - Re: Charpentier, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- B. Shane's Retirement, 1971-1976 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Montreal Joint Board: Grievance Committee, 1969-1970 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Minutes, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Committee for Fair Postal Rates, 1969-1970 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Industry Wide Bargaining, 1967-1970 (Box 11, Folder 13)
- Correspondence, 1969-1971 (Box 11, Folder 14)
- M. Charpentier, 1968-1969 (Box 11, Folder 15)
- Democratic Action League, 1969-1970 (Box 11, Folder 16)
- Bulletin, 1965-1970 (Box 11, Folder 17)
- Local 240, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 18)
- Andre Corneau vs. Cecile Daoust, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 19)
- Yves Bacon vs. Local 205, 1969-1971 (Box 11, Folder 20)
- Andre Croneau vs. Local 439, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 21)
- Andre Corneau vs. Local 205, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 22)
- Andre Croneau vs. Local 262, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 23)
- Jim MacDonald, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 24)
- Workmen's Compensation Act, 1968-1971 (Box 11, Folder 25)
- Union Within the Union, 1961 (Box 11, Folder 26)
- Two Years Up, 1968-1970 (Box 11, Folder 27)
- Andre Corneau, 1969-1970 (Box 11, Folder 28)
- Appeal Committee, 1968-1971 (Box 11, Folder 29)
- Ginette Gutton, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 30)
- Falcon, Jesus, 1969-1970 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Elections 1971 - Appeals (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Elections 1971 - Appeals (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Lafrance, Gerard; Deschesnes, Richard, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Joe Proce, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- De Repentigny, Marcel, Re: Elections 1968, 1968-1969 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- De Repentigny, Marcel; Re: Elections 1968, 1967-1968 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Manel, Maurice; Re: Charges Against De Repentigny, 1967-1971 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Manel, Maurice; Re: Charges Against De Repentigny, 1968-1971 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Perreault, Lionel; Re: Charges Against Marcel Labelle, 1968-1971 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- Boyt, Reynald; Goedike, John; Lelong, Willy, 1968-1969 (Box 12, Folder 11)
- Charges; Re: Elections 1965, 1965-1966 (Box 12, Folder 12)
- De Repentigny, Marcel; Re: Appeal Against Fine by Pressers' Local 439, 1967-1969 (Box 12, Folder 13)
- De Repentigny, Marcel; Re: Reprimands, 1966-1968 (Box 12, Folder 14)
- Charges; Re: Cutters Working Illegal Hours, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 15)
- Appeal of 10 Cutters; Re: Elections, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 16)
- Labelle, Guy; Re: Appeal of the Decision of Local 439, 1967-1968 (Box 12, Folder 17)
- Corneau, Andre; Re: Charges Against Manel, 1968-1971 (Box 12, Folder 18)
- Local 235: Personnel, 1966-1971 (Box 12, Folder 19)
- Local 236: Board of Directors, 1967-1971 (Box 12, Folder 20)
- Contract 1969: Working Material, 1969-1970 (Box 12, Folder 21)
- Contract 1969: Working Material, 1969-1972 (Box 12, Folder 22)
- Contract 1969: Working Material, 1969-1972 (Box 12, Folder 23)
- Embroidery, 1940-1946 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Embroidery, 1944-1946 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Embroidery - Agreements & General, 1963-1966 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Embroidery - Agreements & General, 1960-1963 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Contracts - Individual Embroidery Manufacturers, 1967-1970 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Contracts - Individual Embroidery Manufacturers, 1964-1967 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Contracts - Individual Embroidery Manufacturers, 1964-1967 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Contracts - Individual Embroidery Manufacturers, 1937-1963 (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Modern Swiss Embroidery Works, Inc., 1969-1974 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Modern Swiss Embroidery Works, Inc., 1966-1969 (Box 13, Folder 10)
- Contracts - Swiss Embroidery, 1969-1970 (Box 13, Folder 11)
- Contracts - Swiss Embroidery, 1966-1971 (Box 13, Folder 12)
- Contracts - Swiss Embroidery, 1958-1965 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- Modern Swiss, 1961-1965 (Box 13, Folder 14)
- Correspondence with Belt Manufacturers, 1964-1969 (Box 13, Folder 15)
- Correspondence with Belt Manufacturers, 1960-1963 (Box 13, Folder 16)
- Correspondence with Belt Manufacturers, 1970-1971 (Box 13, Folder 17)
- Correspondence with Embroidery Manufacturers, 1964-1969 (Box 13, Folder 18)
- Correspondence with Embroidery Manufacturers, 1941-1971 (Box 13, Folder 19)
- Correspondence with Members, 1970-1971 (Box 13, Folder 20)
- Death Benefit Fund - General, 1961-1971 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Death and Benefit Fund - General, 1970-1971 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Decorative Linens, 1967-1970 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Decorative Linens, 1957-1967 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Decorative Linens, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Decorative Linens, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Deluxe Embroidery, 1966-1969 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- Deluxe Embroidery, 1966-1969 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- Deluxe Embroidery, 1957-1968 (Box 14, Folder 9)
- Deluxe Embroidery, 1963-1974 (Box 14, Folder 10)
- Deluxe Embroidery, 1960-1965 (Box 14, Folder 11)
- Liquidated Damage, 1970-1972 (Box 14, Folder 12)
- Dues - General, 1966-1970 (Box 14, Folder 13)
- Dues- General, 1963-1972 (Box 14, Folder 14)
- Elections, 1965-1968 (Box 14, Folder 15)
- Executive Board - Local 315: Copies of Minutes, 1970-1971 (Box 14, Folder 16)
- Executive Board - Local 315, 1970-1971 (Box 14, Folder 17)
- F.A.M.A. - General, 1957-1968 (Box 14, Folder 18)
- F.A.M.A - General, 1934-1961 (Box 14, Folder 19)
- F.A.M.A. - General, 1934-1971 (Box 14, Folder 20)
- Health Centre - Correspondence, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 21)
- Health Centre - Annual Statement, 1961-1967 (Box 14, Folder 22)
- Health Centre - Annual Statement, 1961-1971 (Box 14, Folder 23)
- Joint Committee, 1965-1967 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Joint Committee Meeting: Minutes, 1954-1955 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Joint Committee Meeting: Minutes, 1953 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Joint Committee Meeting: Minutes, 1952 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Joint Committee Meeting: Minutes, 1951 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Joint Committee Meeting: Minutes, 1950-1955 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Joint Committee Meeting: Minutes, 1944 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- Joint Committee Meeting: Minutes, 1943 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- Joint Committee Meeting: Minutes, 1942 (Box 15, Folder 9)
- Joint Committee Meeting: Minutes, 1941 (Box 15, Folder 10)
- Joint Committee Meeting: Minutes, 1940 (Box 15, Folder 11)
- Joint Committee Meeting: Minutes, 1939 (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Joint Committee Meeting: Minutes, 1938 (Box 15, Folder 13)
- Joint Committee Meeting: Minutes, 1937 (Box 15, Folder 14)
- Joint Committee Meeting: Minutes, 1936 (Box 15, Folder 15)
- Joint Committee Meeting: Minutes, 1935 (Box 15, Folder 16)
- Joint Committee Statistics - General, 1949-1960 (Box 15, Folder 17)
- Donations, 1939-1964 (Box 15, Folder 18)
- Donations, 1936-1951 (Box 15, Folder 19)
- J.J. Spector, Q.C., 1950-1964 (Box 15, Folder 20)
- Jewish Labor Committee, 1951-1960 (Box 15, Folder 21)
- Jewish Labor Committee, 1941-1951 (Box 15, Folder 22)
- Joint Application to Regional Labour Board, 1943 (Box 15, Folder 23)
- Embroidery Workers, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 24)
- Montreal Typographical Union, 1937-1938 (Box 15, Folder 25)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1962-1970 (Box 15, Folder 26)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1953-1962 (Box 15, Folder 27)
- Miscellaneous Booklets, 1933-1957 (Box 15, Folder 28)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1940-1952 (Box 15, Folder 29)
- Joint Committee - General, 1956-1968 (Box 15, Folder 30)
- Joint Committee - General, 1951-1955 (Box 15, Folder 31)
- Joint Committee - General, 1935-1951 (Box 15, Folder 32)
- Mannish Type Suits, 1940-1941 (Box 15, Folder 33)
- Elections & Convention, 1938-1962 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Elections, 1940 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Elections, 1958-1959 (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Elections, 1942 (Box 16, Folder 4)
- Joint Committee: Minutes, 1963-1964 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Joint Committee: Minutes, 1960-1963 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Joint Committee: Minutes, 1958-1959 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- Elections, 1956 (Box 16, Folder 8)
- Elections, 1953 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- Elections - 1971 (Box 16, Folder 10)
- Elections - 1971 (Box 16, Folder 11)
- Elections 1950 (Box 16, Folder 12)
- Elections - 1944 (Box 16, Folder 13)
- Elections - 1947 (Box 16, Folder 14)
- Canadian Coordinating Conference, 1960-1961 (Box 16, Folder 15)
- Canadian Coordinating Conference, 1958-1960 (Box 16, Folder 16)
- Canadian Coordinating Conference, 1958 (Box 16, Folder 17)
- Canadian Coordinating Convention Report, 1954 (Box 16, Folder 18)
- Canadian Coordinating Convention Report, 1954 (Box 16, Folder 19)
- Canadian Coordinating Committee, 1950-1958 (Box 16, Folder 20)
- Canadian Children's Wear, 1963 (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Canadian Children's Wear: Locals 262 and 485, 1963-1966 (Box 17, Folder 2)
- Canadian Children's Wear: Plant No. 2, Richmond, Quebec, 1963 (Box 17, Folder 3)
- Canadian Children's Wear Ltd.: Plant No. 1, Montreal, Quebec, 1962-1964 (Box 17, Folder 4)
- Canadian Children's Wear Ltd.: Plant No. 1, Montreal, Quebec, 1962 (Box 17, Folder 5)
- Newspapers, 1961-1963 (Box 17, Folder 6)
- Children's Wear File, 1962-1963 (Box 17, Folder 7)
- Memorandum of Agreement, 1951 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  August 29, 1951
- Memorandum of Agreement Between Montreal Dress Manufacturers' Guild and Montreal Joint Board Dressmakers' Union, 1956-1957 (Box 17, Folder 9)
- Documents, 1953-1963 (Box 17, Folder 10)
- Clips, 1960-1963 (Box 17, Folder 11)
- Credentials, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 12)
- Convention Call, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 13)
- Correspondence, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 14)
- Quebec Federation of Labor, 1969-1970 (Box 17, Folder 15)
- Quebec Federation of Labor, 1955-1957 (Box 17, Folder 16)
- Quebec Federation of Labor, 1969 (Box 17, Folder 17)
- Quebec Federation of Labor, 1962-1965 (Box 17, Folder 18)
- Quebec Federation of Labor, 1960-1963 (Box 17, Folder 19)
- Quebec Federation of Labor, 1958-1959 (Box 17, Folder 20)
- Quebec Federation of Labor, 1947-1957 (Box 17, Folder 21)
- Quebec Federation of Labor, 1971-1975 (Box 17, Folder 22)
- Labor World, Published by Quebec Federation of Labor, 1958 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- Quebec Federation of Labor: Credit Union, 1965 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  August 26, 1965
- Joint Commission - General, 1965-1971 (Box 18, Folder 3)
- Joint Commission - General, 1957-1965 (Box 18, Folder 4)
- The Joint Commission for the Dress Industry, 1970-1971 (Box 18, Folder 5)
- The Joint Commission for the Dress Industry: Financial Statements, 1968-1969 (Box 18, Folder 6)
- Joint Commission - Statements, 1954-1957 (Box 18, Folder 7)
- Joint Commission Statistics, 1967-1971 (Box 18, Folder 8)
- Joint Commission Analysis, 1971-1976 (Box 18, Folder 9)
- Joint Commission Analysis, 1971-1975 (Box 18, Folder 10)
- Joint Commission - Financial Statements, 1962-1968 (Box 18, Folder 11)
- Joint Commission - Financial Statements, 1955-1961 (Box 18, Folder 12)
- Joint Commission - Financial Statements, 1952-1955 (Box 18, Folder 13)
- Joint Commission Code, 1946-1967 (Box 18, Folder 14)
- Joint Commission: Cost of Living Bonus Conversation, 1952 (Box 18, Folder 15)
- Joint Commission, 1966-1971 (Box 18, Folder 16)
- Death Benefit Funds, 1950-1953 (Box 18, Folder 17)
- Bonding Personnel, 1952-1962 (Box 18, Folder 18)
- Staff Retirement Fund ILGWU Correspondence, 1950-1968 (Box 18, Folder 19)
- Staff Retirement Fund ILGWU Correspondence, 1946-1950 (Box 18, Folder 20)
- Staff Retirement Fund, 1956-1971 (Box 18, Folder 21)
- Retirement Fund - General, 1952-1971 (Box 18, Folder 22)
- Retirement Fund - General, 1964-1968 (Box 18, Folder 23)
- Retirement Fund, 1965-1971 (Box 18, Folder 24)
- Retirement Fund, 1958-1962 (Box 18, Folder 25)
- Retirement Fund, 1953-1958 (Box 18, Folder 26)
- Pressers' Meeting, 1972-1975 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Pressers' Meeting, 1972-1973 (Box 19, Folder 2)
- Pressers' Meeting, 1972-1975 (Box 19, Folder 3)
- Pressers' Meetings, 1971-1972 (Box 19, Folder 4)
- Dress, Local 439: Board Minutes, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 5)
- Dress, Local 439: Board Minutes, 1973-1974 (Box 19, Folder 6)
- Dress, Local 439: Board Minutes, 1972-1973 (Box 19, Folder 7)
- Copies of Pressers: Executive Board Local 262, 1971-1976 (Box 19, Folder 8)
- Copies of Pressers: Executive Board Local 262, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 9)
- Poirier Gerard - Personnel, 1953-1971 (Box 19, Folder 10)
- Pressers Welfare Fund, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 11)
- Pressers Welfare Fund, 1970-1972 (Box 19, Folder 12)
- Pressers Welfare Fund, 1974-1975 (Box 19, Folder 13)
- Pressers' Welfare Fund, 1972-1974 (Box 19, Folder 14)
- Pressers' Welfare Fund, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 15)
- Provincial Department of Labor, 1942-1966 (Box 19, Folder 16)
- Group Insurance, 1963 (Box 19, Folder 17)
- Blue Cross, 1964-1970 (Box 19, Folder 18)
- Blue Cross, 1960-1964 (Box 19, Folder 19)
- Blue Cross, 1952-1960 (Box 19, Folder 20)
- Blue Cross, 1952-1953 (Box 19, Folder 21)
- Blue Cross, 1949-1952 (Box 19, Folder 22)
- Press Releases: Publicity, 1957-1970 (Box 20, Folder 1)
- Press Releases, 1952-1958 (Box 20, Folder 2)
- Press Releases: Publicity, 1946-1951 (Box 20, Folder 3)
- Publicity, 1959 (Box 20, Folder 4)
- Publicity, 1959 (Box 20, Folder 5)
- Publicity, 1959-1960 (Box 20, Folder 6)
- Dress Industry - Collective Agreement, 1972-1975 (Box 20, Folder 7)
- Clippings, 1958-1959 (Box 20, Folder 8)
- Press Releases to Mass Media, 1969-1971 (Box 20, Folder 9)
- Press Releases to Mass Media, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 10)
- Press Releases to Mass Media, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 11)
- Press Releases to Mass Media, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 12)
- Press Releases to Mass Media, 1966-1968 (Box 20, Folder 13)
- Publicity from Mass Media, 1966-1967 (Box 20, Folder 14)
- Souvenir Program, 1952 (Box 20, Folder 15)
- Souvenir Program, 1952 (Box 20, Folder 16)
- Assessments and Dues, 1963-1971 (Box 20, Folder 17)